[{"answer": "Hopefully, in the White House.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Say we do all survive two years of campaign help, where does that leave our family?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "I actually didn't know.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "That must make you feel great, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "You know, I think if it had been Hillary's story, I probably wouldn't have done it, as much as I admire her.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "It -- was that deliberate in your -- back of your mind?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, that's one of the things our series is trying to find out.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, I suppose it could, but you sound more optimistic than I feel.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Do you feel like the whole barrier to the concept of a female president may change very quickly?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, I do.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Do you remember that period at all, his political life?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "EAVER: My father told us a wonderful story.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "What did that do to your view of politics?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Oh, no, I think he was heartbroken for the country.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Was your father quietly smug when Nixon came crashing down, that his instinct about him had been proven right?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "You look up there.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Where do we look?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "That's an interesting question.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "I mean, do you feel more empathy with the pressures that go with that kind of job?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I thought it was very interesting last week that he said he's really concentrated on policy, because that makes sense to me, with his character.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "How do you -- how do you think President Obama's done?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "You look terrific.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "And how do I look?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "And apart from Melanie Griffith's extraordinary hair in that movie, but that was a great -- that was a great comedy role, really, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Magic?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "You know, I think I did.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Is this where you got the love of the business, do you think?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Well, I think fame is the least valuable thing that a successful career gives you.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Do you -- does it diminish what used to be stars on pedestals?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Your mother was English, I discovered literally seconds before we went on the air, very exciting moment when I discovered it.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "You know, how could they possibly tell that this is -- that this is something noble, you know, and difficult to achieve?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "It's actually -- 28.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Gosh, I don't really know.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "You're in a business, you know, where divorce come and go like sort of Number 9 buses, how have you managed to avoid that pitfall?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "It was all kind of crazy.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Or was it honestly more fun being the ne'er-do-well?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Do you know, I'm very, very happy today.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "How the devil are you?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "You do.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "I look different in that clip, huh?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the -- what happened in the weekend was just an administrative finality.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "How do you feel now that you're officially a single man again?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, the limited amount of time I spend in reality I quite enjoy.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "How is your life in reality at the moment?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember that interview very distinctly, Piers.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Have you become, you know, a little less excited about the whole nature of fame and celebrity?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Is there something society should do to try and put a lid on this before we all go completely mad?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "There isn't one, I don't think.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What's the point of it all?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Are you an American resident yet?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I love the American people, all of them, every single individual.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Is America refusing to accept you as one of its own then, Russell?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Pretty good, mostly.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "How is your temper at the moment?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I want to be editor of \"The New Yorker\" and the youngest freelance journalist to be published in \"The New York Times,\" \"L.A. Times\" and \"The Chicago Tribune.\"", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What is it, Munchkin?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, it was a promise that I made to myself when I was 10.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "ORGAN: \"The Wishing Spell,\" why have you written a fairy tale book?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Well, the plot is it's about two kids going to the fairy tale world through a magic story book.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Tell me the narrative?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if there's anything I could say to them.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What do you say to them?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Well, I think at first, those quotes don't say it.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And what would you say to yourself as a 14 year old boy now, if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Oh, I think that was an amazing endorsement.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "What do you feel about the way America has moved and the president's endorsement?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "I'm 22 and an actor.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Are you standing firmly by your president?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "You can vote.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "You're asking my political advice?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I was in high school.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Are you very political?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "No, I just think it's annoying.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Is it too dangerous to be a young, handsome \"Glee\" star pontificating about politics?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "So definitely coming back?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "ORGAN: You weren't just dropping some terrible bombshell?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "No, maybe a letter or two, but this time -- no.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "You're not going to remove the glee from \"Glee\" for millions of young viewers?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I just like progress.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Are you having a good time with all this or?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "You know, don't dilly dally.", "docId": "120728pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "And the moral of that is?", "qSentId": 655}]